meet mr. Finnegan one burger rare on the
inside but charred he seldom satisfied
just a and often disappointed we
were glad when mr. Finnegan chose
Prudential for life insurance and
especially pleased when he came back the
fact is more people come back to
Prudential for another piece of the rock
than ever gets started with most other
life insurance companies five out of
every ten policies we offer for people
who already have a piece of the rock and
I find something I like I stick with it
but don't you let up Prudential when you
think about your financial security see
a Prudential agent come to a company
that
come back to Prudential Insurance